Ben Behrman

♥ United States ■ bbehrman10@gmail.com □ 908-967-1939 m in/bbehrman10

SUMMARY

Experienced engineering and partner relations professional with a passion for connecting and enabling growth through technology. Fluent in both cloud and web3 technologies. Highly effective at operating in cross functional environments. I love to help developers accomplish their goals.

EXPERIENCE

Partner Integrations Engineer

Unstoppable Domains

August 2022 - January 2023, REMOTE

- · Supported and maintained integrations and developer relations.
- · Wrote pull requests, delivered workshops and presentations to hackathons
- · Built and managed production NPM libraries.
- · Integrated 166 applications across 153 different partners.

Staff & Senior Cloud Engineer, I-Team Code Innovate

Oracle

- · Ran over 40 customized cloud workshops as part of the Code Innovate Program.
- Drove customer enablement & consumption through 1–1 technical assistance.
- · Planned, Created Oracle Cloud learning materials & blog posts.

Solutions Engineer, Cloud Solution Hubs

Oracle

August 2018 - June 2020, Burlington, MA

June 2020 - June 2022, REMOTE

- Designed and built proof of concepts as part of an Oracle Cloud Solution.
- \cdot Led an internal applications unit in charge of building applications to assist in the day to day of work.
- · Co-founder of Hubs for Humanity a cloud assistance program tailored for charities and socially driven causes.

SKILLS

Front end: Javascript, Typescript, React, Vue, HTML, CSS, MUI, Web3.js, Ethers.js, ThirdWeb.js

Back end: Node, Solidity, Python, Go, Java, SQL, Postgresql, Ruby, Oracle DB, Hardhat, Truffle, APIs

DevOps & Platforms: Webpack, NPM, Git, Oracle Cloud, Postman

Soft Skills: Cross Functional, Collaborate, Evangelize, Adoption, Advocacy, Empathy, Leadership, Public Speaking, Technical Education & Training, Technical Writing

PROJECTS

NFTickets

EthDenver · February 2022 - March 2022

- · NFT ickets an NFT Ticketing platform for artists to control their ticket sales and for their fans to own their fandom.
- · Built on & secured by the Polygon Blockchain.
- · Winner of a Polygon Technologies Bounty, Runner up for the Chainlink Bounty Prize.

Crypt.IO

Oracle · November 2021 - February 2022

- · Built a chain analysis tool powered by several Oracle Products for the MadHacks Hackathon.
- \cdot Visualized the web of transactions related to a provided wallet.
- · Regional Finalist for the US Region.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Arts Computer Science

Sarah Lawrence College Bronxville, NY · 2017

COURSEWORK

4 Quantum Computing Courses

MIT xPro · 2021 · Quantum Computing

Lab work using Quantum Computing QBIT simulations as well as discussions related to theory and discovery. Intro to Quantum Computing, Practical Realities of Quantum, Quantum Algorithms, and Requirements for Large Scale Universal Quantum.

3 Leadership Courses

MIT xPro · 2021 · Leadership

Passed 3 courses related to building one's leadership skills in an organizational environment. Role play, written, and discussion activities. Understanding Organizational Structures, Negotiating and Applying Influence, and Discovering and Implementing your Leadership Strengths.